ha the the
公顷的
the more
更
the last time
最后一次
we talked about the you the representation
我们谈到了你的陈述
%uh linear time-invariant systems through the convolution song
通过卷积首歌％呃线性时不变系统
in the discrete-time case and the convolution integral in the
在离散时间情况下，该卷积积分
continuous-time
连续时间
case now although the derivation was relatively straightforward
现在情况虽然推导相对简单
in fact the result is really kind of amazing because
其实结果是有点惊人真的是因为
what it tells us is that for linear time-invariant systems
它告诉我们的是，对于线性时不变系统
if we know the response to the system to a single in polls
如果我们知道响应于该系统，以在调查单
at equal 0 or in fact that any other time
于等于0或实际上任何其他时间
then we can determine from that its response
那么我们可以从确定其响应
to an arbitrary input through the use of convolution furthermore
通过使用卷积此外任意输入
what we'll see as the course develops is that in fact
我们会看到随着课程的发展是，在事实
the class a linear time-invariant systems is a very rich class
类线性时不变系统是一个非常丰富的类
there are lots of systems that have that property
有很多的系统，具有该属性
and in addition there are lots a very interesting things that you can do with
而除了有很多很有趣的东西，你可以用做
linear time-invariant systems
线性时不变系统
in today's lecture
在今天的讲座
what I'd like to begin with is focusing
我想首先是重点
on convolution as an algebraic operation
卷积为代数运算
and will see that it has a number of algebraic properties then in turn
以及将看到它具有许多代数性质的再依次
have important implications for
有重要意义
linear time-invariant systems then we'll turn
线性时不变系统然后我们会转
to a discussion or what the
以讨论或什么
characterization %uh linear time-invariant systems
表征％呃线性时不变系统
through convolution implies
通过卷积暗示
in terms of the relationship various other system properties
关系中的其他各种系统性能方面
to the impulse response let me begin by
脉冲响应首先，我要
reminding you love the basic result that we
提醒你爱的基本结果，我们
develop last time which is the convolution some
制定最后一次这是一些卷积
in discrete-time as
在离散时间作为
I indicate here and
我在此说明，并
the convolution integral in continuous-time
在连续时间卷积积分
in and what the convolution some more the convolution integral tells us
在什么卷积一些卷积积分告诉我们
is how to relate the output
是如何与输出
to the input and to the system impulse response
到输入和系统的脉冲响应
and the expression looks
和表达式看起来
basically the same in continuous-time and discrete-time
基本上在连续时间和离散时间相同
and I remind you also that we talked about a graphical interpretation
我提醒你也是我们谈到了一个图形化的解释
where essentially to graphically
其中基本上以图形
interpret convolution required for
需要解释的卷积
was developed in terms
在计算开发
or taking the system impulse response
或采取系统的脉冲响应
flipping it sliding it past the input
它翻转滑动过去的输入
and with positioned appropriately depending on the
并与定位的适当取决于
value of the independent variable for which were computing
方法乃计算自变量的值
the convolution and then multiplying and
卷积，然后乘以与
summing in the discrete-time case or integrating
总结在离散时间情况下或整合
in the continuous-time case now
在连续时间的情况下，现在
convolution as an algebraic operation
卷积为代数运算
has a number or important properties
有一些或重要性质
one of the properties of convolution
卷积的特性之一
is that it is what is referred to as commuted
是，它是被称为减
community here means that
社区在这里意味着
we can think either a convo loving
我们可以认为无论是康沃爱
X with age or H with axe
X而年龄或H与斧头
and the order in which that's done
和顺序这样做了
doesn't affect the output result so summarized here
不影响输出结果这里如此概括
is what the community operation is
是社会运行的是什么
in discrete-time or in continuous-time
在离散时间或连续时间
and it says as I just indicated that
它说，正如我刚才指出，
x7 convolved with a chip and
X7为卷积芯片和
is equal to a chip and convolved
等于一个芯片和卷积
with exit or the same course
用exit或同一门课程
in continuous-time and in fact
在连续时间与实际上
in the lecture last time
在讲座最后一次
we worked an example where we had indiscreet I'm an impulse response which
我们的工作的例子，我们不得不指手画脚，我是一个脉冲响应的
was an exponential
是一个指数
and an input which is a unit step
和一个输入是单位阶跃
and in the text what you'll find is
并在文中你会发现什么是
the same example work except in that case
除了在这种情况下，同样的例子工作
the input is the exponential and the system impulse response is the step
输入是指数和系统的脉冲响应是步
and that corresponds to the example in the text
和对应于该实施例中的文本
which is example 3.1
这是例如3.1
and what happens in an example is that in fact
以及发生了什么的一个例子是，在实际上
what you'll see is that the same result
什么，你会看到的是，同样的结果
occurs an example 3.1 as we generated
的发生是由于我们生成的示例3.1
in the lecture and there's a similar comparison
在讲座中，有一个类似的比较
in continuous-time this example was worked in
在连续时间这个例子是在工作
lecture and this example
讲座和这个例子
is work in the text in other words
在工作​​中，换句话说文
the text works the example where the system
文字作品的例子，该系统
impulse response is
脉冲响应是
unit step and the input is an exponential
单位工序和输入是一个指数
right now the community property as I said tells us
现在我说，小区物业告诉我们
that the order in which we do convolution
在我们做卷积的顺序
doesn't affect the result to the convolution
不影响结果的卷积
the same is true for continuous-time and discrete-time
在连续时间和离散时间也是如此
and in fact for the other algebraic properties that I'll talk about
而事实上对于其它的代数性质，我将谈谈
the results are exactly the same for continuous-time and discrete-time
结果是完全相同的连续时间和离散时间
so in fact what we can do is
所以其实我们可以做的是
drop the independent variable as an argument
掉落自变量作为参数
so that we suppress any kinda difference between continuous and discrete-time
让我们压抑连续和离散时间之间的任何差别还挺
and suppressing be independent variable
和抑制是独立变量
within state the community property as I've
州内，因为我已经在小区物业
rewritten it here just X convulsed with age because
改写在这里仅售X忍俊不禁随着年龄的增长，因为
H involved with the ex the same in continuous-time
ħ涉及与前相同的连续时间
and discrete-time now
和离散时间现在
the derivation to the community property is
推导到社区物业
more less amount you bro which you can follow through in the book it involves
你的兄弟，你可以在它涉及的书跟进更量少
soem changes variables and
SOEM改变变量和
in some things that sort
在一些事情的排序
what I'd like to focus on with that and other properties
我想专注于与和其他属性
is not the derivation which you can see in the tax
是不是推导，您可以在税收看
by rather the interpretation
由宁解释
so we have the community property and now there are two other
所以我们有小区物业，现在有两个
important algebraic properties one being
重要的代数性质的一个是
what is referred to as the associative property
什么被称为缔合特性
which tells us that if we have X convulsed with
它告诉我们，如果我们有X个笑得
the result ok involving h1 with h2
结果确定涉及H1与H2
that's exactly the same as X convolved with h1
这是完全一样的为X卷积H1
and that result involved with h2
并参与了H2的结果
and what this permits is
以及这是允许
for us to write for example ex-convict alt with h1
让我们来写，例如刑满释放中高音与H1
involved with h2 without any ambiguity
参与H2毫不含糊
because it doesn't matter from the associative property
因为它没有从相关属性重要
how we grew the terms together
我们如何长大的条款一起
the third important property is what is referred to as the distributive property
第三个重要的属性是什么被称为分配律
namely the fact the convolution distributes over addition
即事实上的卷积分布在除
and what I mean by that is what i've indicated
什么我的意思是，我所指出
here on the slide dead if
这里在幻灯片上死了，如果
I think or X convo with the psalm
我认为或X康沃的诗篇
of h1n h2 that's identical
H1N H2那是相同的
to first involving X with h1
首先涉及到X而H1
also can bombing X with h2 and then
也可以轰炸X而H2，然后
adding the two together and that result
添加两个在一起，那结果
will be the same as this result
将是相同的，因此这个结果
so convolution is community
因此卷积社区
associative and it distributes over addition
联想并将其分发给了另外
three very important algebraic properties and
三个非常重要的代数性质和
by the way there are other algebraic operations that have
顺便说存在具有其它代数运算
that same property for example multiplication
同样的属性，例如乘法
numbers is likewise commuted to associative
数字同样改判为关联
and distributed now
而现在分布
let's look at what these three properties
让我们来看看什么是这三个属性
imply a specifically for linear time-invariant systems
意味着一个专门针对线性时不变系统
and as we'll see the the implications
正如我们将看到的影响
are both very interesting and very important
都是非常有趣和非常重要的
let's begin with the community property
让我们开始与小区物业
and consider in particular
并特别考虑
a system with an impulse response age
带有脉冲响应年龄的系统
and I represent that by simply writing the H inside the box
我代表通过简单地写在H盒内
an input tax and an output then
进项税和输出，然后
which is X convulsed with age
这为X忍俊不禁随着年龄的增长
now since this operation is commuted to
现在因为这个操作是改判
I can right is that affects convolved with a I can write
我可以用鼠标右键是影响卷积与我可以写
H convolved with ex and that would correspond
ħ卷积前，而将对应
to a system with impulse response
用脉冲响应系统
X and input H and output then
X和输入H和输出，然后
age involved with ex
涉及年龄与前
so the community property
所以小区物业
tells us therefore a linear time-invariant system
告诉我们，因此一个线性时不变系统
the system output is independent
系统的输出是独立
all which function we call the input
所有这些功能，我们称之为输入
and which function we call the impulse response kind amazing actually
以及功能我们称之为脉冲响应那种惊人的实际
we can interchange the role input and impulse response
我们可以互换角色的输入和脉冲响应
and from input or permit output point of view
而且从输入或许可证输出点
the output for the system doesn't care
该系统的输出不关心
now furthermore if we combine the community property
而且现在如果我们结合社区物业
with the associative property we get another very interesting result
与关联属性，我们得到另一个非常有趣的结果
namely that if we have two linear time-invariant systems in cascade
即，如果我们有两个线性时不变系统的级联
the overall system is independent of the order in which they are cascaded
整个系统是独立于它们所级联的顺序
and in fact in either case the Cascade can be
而事实上在两种情况下，梯级可以是
collapsed into a single system
折叠成一个单一的系统
to see this let's first consider
看到这个我们先考虑
the Cascade or two systems one with impulse response h1
级联或两个系统之一，脉冲响应H1
the other with impulse response h2 and
另用脉冲响应H2和
the outputted the first system is then
的输出的第一系统是​​再
X convulsed with h1
X笑得H1
and then that is the input to the second system
然后是输入到所述第二系统
and so the output a bad is that result
所以输出一个糟糕的是，结果
convolved with h2
卷积H2
so this is the result of cascading the two
因此，这是层叠的2的结果
and now we can use the associative property
现在我们可以使用关联属性
to rewrite this and as
重写这个和
X involved with h1
X涉及H1
involved with h2 where we grew these two terms together
涉及H2，我们长大这两个名词在一起
and so using the associative property
所以使用关联属性
we now can collapse that into a single system
我们现在可以说垮到一个单一的系统
with an input which is ax an impulse response which is h1 convolved with h2
一个输入是斧子是H1卷积H2的脉冲响应
and the output is then ex-convict all with
和输出，然后刑满释放全部用
the result that those two can borrow
结果，这两个可以借
next we can apply the community property
接下来我们可以将小区物业
and the commuter property says we could write
和通勤物业说，我们可以这样写
this impulse response that way or we can write it this way
这种冲激响应的方式，或者我们可以这样写
and since convolutions community the resulting output will be exactly the
而且由于回旋社区的输出结果将是完全
same
同
and so these resulting output will be exactly the same
因此这些输出结果将是完全相同的
and now once again we can use the associative property
而现在我们再次可以使用关联属性
to group these two terms together
以组这两个名词在一起
and X convulsed with h2
和X笑得H2
corresponds to putting X first through the system h2
相当于把X表示先通过系统H2
and then an output through the system h1 and so
然后通过系统h1和这样一个输出
finally applying the associative property again as I just outlined
最后应用结合性事，是我刚刚概述
we can expand that system back into
我们可以扩展该系统回
two systems in cascade with h2 first
两个系统级联用H2第一
NH one second
NH1秒
okay well that involves a certain amount love algebraic manipulation
还好以及涉及一定数额的爱代数运算
and that it's not the algebraic manipulation that's important is the
而且它不是代数运算这是重要的是
result that it's important
导致它的重要
and what the result says to reiterate this if I have to
和什么样的结果，说要重申这一点，如果我有
linear time-invariant systems in cascade
线性时不变系统的级联
I can cascade them in any order and the result is the same
我可以级联以任何顺序和结果是一样的
now you might think well G maybe that actually applies the systems in general
现在你可能会认为G井也许这实际上是应用系统一般
whether you put them this way or that way but in fact as we talked about last
无论你把它们这样或那样的方式，但事实上，我们谈到最后
time
时间
and I illustrated with an example
我用一个例子说明
in general if the system is not linear
一般来说，如果系统不是线性
the systems are not linear and time-invariant then
该系统不是线性时不变则
the order in which they are cascaded is important to the interpretation of the
它们被级联的顺序是很重要的的解释
overall system
整个系统
for example one system took the square root
例如，一个系统作为平方根
any other system double the input
任何其他系统两倍的输入
taking the square root and then doubling
求平方根，然后再加倍
gives us a different answer doubling first and then taking the square root
给了我们一个不同的答案加倍，然后再取平方根
and of course one can construct much more elaborate example
当然可以构建更复杂的例子
net so it's a property very particular to linear time-invariant systems and
净所以这是一个属性非常特殊的线性时不变系统和
also
还
one that we will exploit many many times as we go through this material
一个我们会利用很多很多次，因为我们通过这个材料
the final property related to
相关的最终属性
interconnection systems that I want to just indicate
我想只显示互连系统
develops ida the distributive property
开发IDA分配律
and what it applies to is an interpretation
它适用于什么是解释
%uh the interconnection of systems in parallel
系统并行％呃联网
recall there the parallel combination
记得有并联组合
systems corresponds is a indicate here
系统对应的是一个显示在这里
to a system in which we simultaneously feed the input into
到一个系统中，我们同时喂输入到
h1 nh2 these representing the impulse responses
H1 NH2这些代表的脉冲响应
and then the outputs our song and to form
然后输出我们的歌，并形成
the overall output and
整体输出和
using the fact their convolution distributes
使用事实上，他们的卷积所分销
over addition we can rewrite yes
除了以上我们可以重写是
as X involved with h1
为X涉及H1
plus h2
更多H2
and when we do that then we can recognize this
而当我们这样做，那么我们就可以识别这个
as the output the system with input acts
作为输出的系统具有输入行为
and impulse response which is the sum of these two impulse responses
并且这两个脉冲响应的总和脉冲响应
so for linear time-invariant systems in parallel
所以对于线性时不变系统并行
we can if we choose
我们可以，如果我们选择
replace that interconnection by a single system
更换由一个单一的系统互连
whose impulse response is simply some
其脉冲响应仅仅是一些
those impulse response
这些脉冲响应
okay now we have this very
还好现在我们有了这个非常
powerful representation for linear time-invariant systems
强大的表示线性时不变系统
terms 0 convolution and we've seen so far in this lecture
术语0卷积，我们已经在此讲学迄今为止看到
how convolution and the representation through the impulse response
如何通过脉冲响应卷积和表示
leads to some but important implications for system interconnections
导致了一些，但对于系统互连重要意义
what I like to turn to now are other system properties
我想谈谈现在有其他的系统属性
and see how for linear time-invariant systems in particular
看看如何为线性时不变系统，特别是
other system properties can be Associated
其他的系统属性可以关联
with particular properties or characteristics
与特定的属性或特征
love the system impulse response and what will talk about
喜欢该系统的脉冲响应，什么说说
are a variety of properties will talk about the issue memory will talk about
是各种属性将讨论这个问题的内存将谈论
the issue
问题
portability and will talk about the issue
便携性和会讨论这个问题
causality and also stability
因果性和稳定性也
well let's begin with the issue of memory and the question
好，让我们开始与内存的问题，这个问题
now is what are the implications
现在什么样的影响
for the system impulse response for a linear time-invariant system remember
为一个线性时不变系统的系统脉冲响应记
that we're always imposing that on the system
我们总是施加在系统上
what are the implications on the impulse response if the system
什么是对脉冲响应的影响，如果系统
does or does not have memory
或不具备内存
well we can answer that by looking at
好，我们可以回答这个问题通过查看
the convolution property
卷积财产
and we have here as a reminder the convolution integral
我们这里有一个提醒的卷积积分
which tells us how accept an hour in a chip T-minus
它告诉我们如何在一个芯片上的T减去接受一小时
now are combined to give us y'at
现在相结合，给我们y'at
and what I've illustrated above is
和我上面已经说明是
only general kind of example
只是一般的类的实例
here is except al here is
这里是除了人这里
a chip T-minus now an
芯片现在是一个T型减
to compute the output at any time T
来计算输出在任何时刻T
we would take these two multiply them together
我们将采取这两种它们相乘
and integrate from minus infinity the plus infinity
并从负无穷整合正无穷大
so the question then is what can we say about
所以接下来的问题是我们能说一下
H T the impulse response
H T的脉冲响应
in order to guarantee let's say
为了保证让我们说
that the output depends only on the input at time t
该输出在时刻t只对输入的依赖
well its pretty much obvious from looking
以及其看去几乎明显
at the grabs
在争夺
if we only want the output to depend
如果我们只希望输出依赖
on XO how at Tower equals T
在XO如何在塔等于Ŧ
then a chip T-minus have 0 better
那么芯片的T-减去有0更好
be non-zero only at Tower equals T
是非零仅在塔等于Ŧ
and so the implication is that
所以其含义是，